<sburb>
<classes>
<action class='daveTalk1' sprite='kanaya' command='talk' name='Hablar con Dave.'>
      <args>
      @dave_idle DAVE: ey
      @dave_talk DAVE: vale que pasa
      @dave_talk DAVE: nos hemos dado de lleno con otra burbuja o que
      @kanaya2_idle KANAYA: Pues S&#237;
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: Por Eso Tengo A Este Espectro De Acompa&#241;ante
      @dave_huh DAVE: ah
      @dave_huh DAVE: buenas
      @meenah_wink MEENAH: 
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: &#191;te ha comido la lengua el pez gato?
      @dave_smug DAVE: que ha sido del desparpajo de antes
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: Intenta Portarse Como Mejor Puede Mientras La Escolto
      @kanaya2_happytalk KANAYA: Debo Decir Que No Lo Hace Nada Mal
      @dave_idle DAVE: po fale
      @dave_talk DAVE: ahora ya pasamos del tema este de las burbujas del sue&#241;o no      
	  @dave_talk DAVE: ya ni avisamos ni pensamos en replicas graciosas para el personal total pa que
      @dave_huh DAVE: buah que mas da
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: mejor me quedo donde estoy
      @dave_talk DAVE: que tanto fantasma ya aburre
      @dave_smug DAVE: sin ofender besuga
      @meenah_fish MEENAH: (blancucho cometierra)
      @kanaya2_idle KANAYA: &#161;Chit&#243;n!
      @meenah_wut2 MEENAH: 38(
      @kanaya2_happytalk KANAYA: Por Cierto Qu&#233; Farfullabas Antes De Nuestra Interrupci&#243;n
      @dave_talk DAVE: nada estaba rapeando
      @dave_talk DAVE: currandome unos temas
      @dave_talk DAVE: eres fan de mi repertorio no
      @dave_talk DAVE: te hace escuchar un poco
      @kanaya2_idle KANAYA: ...
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: espera no me digas que no sabes lo que es un rap
      @dave_talk DAVE: es una tradicion de chulos muy nuestra que consiste en decir verdades como pu&#241;os siguiendo cierto ritmo
      @dave_talk DAVE: si te lo curras y marcas tendencia vienen los maderos y te acribillan a balazos
      @dave_talk DAVE: es un acto reflejo no pueden evitarlo
      @dave_talk DAVE: eso quiere decir que vas por buen camino
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: S&#233; Lo Que Es Un Rap Se Parece Bastante A Nuestro Arte Milenario De Torneos De Poes&#237;a
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: Aunque Vuestra Tem&#225;tica No Es Tan Avanzada Como La Nuestra Ni Se Centra Tanto En Reses Fornidas
      @dave_idle DAVE: como que torneos de poesia
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: y me lo dices ahora
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: No S&#233; Tampoco Es Que Me Interese Mucho
      @dave_mad DAVE: pero a ver
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: es la primera noticia que tengo
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: no espera
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: me acuerdo de la vez que rapee con el zumbado aquel
      @kanaya2_idle KANAYA: Mira T&#250; Por D&#243;nde
      @dave_talk DAVE: o sea que podiamos haber hablado de rap en cualquier momento
      @dave_talk DAVE: tu y yo quiero decir
      @dave_talk DAVE: con razon no salia el tema si no hablamos casi nada
      @dave_talk DAVE: tenemos que hablar mas kanaya
      @dave_talk DAVE: asi que ya sabes
      @dave_talk DAVE: manos a la obra
      @dave_talk DAVE: a darle al palique
      @dave_talk DAVE: hasta que el cuerpo aguante
      @kanaya2_idle KANAYA: Eh
      @dave_idle DAVE: ya me has oido
      @dave_smug DAVE: un intercambio de ideas
      @dave_smug DAVE: igual hasta EXPLOTAMOS nuestro potencial
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: aunque haya que chuparle la sangre al otro
      @dave_concern DAVE: y esta mojama no dice nada pero se le quedara grabado en la retina
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: Desconozco El M&#233;todo Que Emplear&#225;s Para Extraer Mi Plasma Sangu&#237;neo Pero Por M&#237; No Hay Problema
      @dave_smug DAVE: si se&#241;or
      @dave_smug DAVE: una peque&#241;a pulla a tu condicion de vampira me gusta empezamos bien
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: Muchas Veces Veo Desdibujada La Sinceridad En Tus Palabras
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: Imagino Que Sigues Cierta Ley No Escrita Que Dice Que Toda Frase Debe Contener Alg&#250;n Comentario Jocoso
      @dave_idle DAVE: ahi le has dado
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: Si En Alg&#250;n Momento Te Apeteciese Hablar Acerca De Nuestros Respectivos Patrimonios Bueno No Me Parecer&#237;a Mal
      @kanaya2_happytalk KANAYA: Si Quieres Luego Me Pongo A Buscar Algo De Poes&#237;a Cl&#225;sica De Autores De Renombre
      @dave_idle DAVE: dios si
      @dave_talk DAVE: seria la hostia no lo siguiente
      @kanaya2_happytalk KANAYA: Decidido Pues
      @dave_talk DAVE: y me tienes que traducir ese galimatias vuestro
      @dave_talk DAVE: como cuando karkat me cuenta sus peliculas 
      @dave_idle DAVE: pero esta vez contigo
      @kanaya2_smirklaugh KANAYA: Eh Claro
      @dave_smug DAVE: ah y quiero que rapees en voz alta
      @kanaya2_facepalm KANAYA: Ah
      @dave_smug DAVE: dale ca&#241;a al bajo y echale mas le&#241;a al micro
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: haz que SIENTA vuestra poesia en carne viva
      @kanaya2_bored KANAYA: Ya Es Tarde Para Echarme Atr&#225;s Verdad
      @meenah_happy MEENAH: aj&#225;
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>   
<action class='daveTalk2' sprite='rose' command='talk' name='Talk to Dave.'>
      <args>
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: whats up with the fish punk troll following kanaya around
      @rose_talk ROSE: Seems she's passing through. Kanaya doesn't want her to cause trouble.
      @dave_huh DAVE: cause trouble
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: what the fuck could she even do here
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: like kick over an old pile of garbage and cause the property value to fall even lower than jack shit
      @dave_smug DAVE: i say let her go nuts
      @rose_talk ROSE: Feel free to take it up with Kanaya.
      @rose_annoyedtalk ROSE: But if you authorize her to flip a bitch, just make sure she's nowhere near my chemistry table. 
      @dave_idle DAVE: yeah
      @dave_talk DAVE: cant be droppin your vials and shit all over the floor
      @dave_talk DAVE: the only one whos got clearance to drop science is me
      @rose_annoyed ROSE: Dork.
      @dave_mad DAVE: dont even hate
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: been shoring up my muthafuckin CRAFT over here
      @rose_annoyedtalk ROSE: I know. I've been in the same room, right over there, listening to you mumble lyrics to yourself for the last couple hours.
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: rose you know what sucks
      @rose_idle ROSE: Yes.
      @rose_talk ROSE: To which sucky thing are you referring?
      @dave_talk DAVE: it kinda just occurred to me
      @dave_talk DAVE: while i was spitting ill verse to no end
      @dave_talk DAVE: i got this weird feeling that i might be getting like
      @dave_huh DAVE: a little dated?
      @rose_coy ROSE: Is this about Terezi?
      @dave_huh DAVE: what
      @dave_mad DAVE: no no
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: dont be disingenuous word girl you know what im saying
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: i mean sorta passe
      @dave_talk DAVE: like a lumbering pop reference dinosaur
      @dave_talk DAVE: remember we are both kind of stuck in 2009
      @dave_talk DAVE: so im like popculturally frozen in that period
      @dave_talk DAVE: all my references feel like they might be getting a little stale
      @dave_talk DAVE: even though the earth ended and all and there was no culture after that point anyway
      @dave_talk DAVE: but still
      @dave_talk DAVE: i can feel it
      @dave_talk DAVE: like in my bones
      @dave_talk DAVE: i just know on some hypothetical earth that kept going my shit is starting to get so lame
      @dave_talk DAVE: and i know it doesnt matter because its just us here so who cares
      @dave_talk DAVE: but i care
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: its a matter of integrity i am a fucking artist
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: like i think if i make one more rap about like some fucking dane cook movie from 2008 to piss karkat off or some tired bullshit like that im going to 
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: i dont know
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: ill just start feeling like a fraud
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: my game might be drying up rose
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: but its not my fault like im totally hostage to this freezedried backlog of cultural garbage that can never move forward again
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: so i have to pick through it like im looting a fucking tomb while still all tryin to act RAP SASSY
      @dave_smug DAVE: like YEAH take THAT motherfuckers
      @dave_concern DAVE: OF THE PAST
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: all in your mass graves somewhere in a dead frogiverse
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: i be representing some god damn STANDARDS about your media do you feel me
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: im depressing myself here
      @dave_talk DAVE: all im saying is it would be cool to have some fresh shit to work with
      @dave_talk DAVE: like just to know
      @dave_talk DAVE: to know what the world would be like in the year it would be for us now
      @dave_talk DAVE: which would be 2011 i guess
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: wow 2011 really
      @dave_huh DAVE: damn
      @dave_talk DAVE: i just want to know what would have happened
      @dave_talk DAVE: theres so much shit we were primed for
      @dave_talk DAVE: it was gonna be exciting
      @dave_talk DAVE: like barack obama just turned president remember that
      @dave_talk DAVE: we never got to see if he fixed the economy
      @dave_talk DAVE: remember how you were dying to see if he would fix the economy you were asking me about it every damn day
      @dave_talk DAVE: just joking nobody gave a shit about that
      @dave_huh DAVE: but like
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: i never got to check out the next batch of stiller jams and see how bad i could mock them
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: we never got to find out how the midnight crew adventure ended
      @dave_mad DAVE: if ever
      @dave_huh DAVE: rose
      @dave_concern DAVE: ROSE??
      @dave_concern DAVE: what the fuck man
      @dave_concern DAVE: whyd you go back to your bottles and shit i was right in the thick of hella elocution
      @dave_concern DAVE: dont give me that
      @dave_concern DAVE: yes
      @dave_concern DAVE: uh yeah
      @dave_concern DAVE: yes i do ACTUALLY want you to come back over here
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: im waiting
      @rose_annoyed ROSE: Fine. Here I am.
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: wow was that so hard
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: this is what civilized people do rose they fucking talk to each other like actually in each others fucking vicinities
      @rose_annoyedtalk ROSE: You just have a tendency to go on for a while. I assumed we progressed to the traditional mumbling monologue stage of Striderian discourse.
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: no thats not even a thing
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: i was actually like
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: trying to get your take
      @rose_idle ROSE: Take on what.
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: i dont even know
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: i bet john would have stuff to say
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: hes probably going through the same frozen fucking caveman from 2009 syndrome as me
      @dave_smug DAVE: actually what am i saying the dude is a caveman from 1997 
      @dave_smug DAVE: hahaha like he could give a shit as long as hes got his cage dvds
      @rose_happytalk ROSE: Oh! I saw him the other night.
      @dave_concern DAVE: what
      @rose_happytalk ROSE: In a dream. It was very brief, only a few minutes. I waved to him and then woke up.
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: whoa what was he doing
      @rose_happytalk ROSE: He was fighting Jack. Actually, he was doing quite well!
      @dave_huh DAVE: oh man
      @dave_smug DAVE: you have to tell me all about this
      @rose_talk ROSE: I will. Later, though. I'd like to get back to work.
      @dave_idle DAVE: ok when
      @dave_idle DAVE: tonight?
      @rose_talk ROSE: I have plans tonight. How about tomorrow.
      @dave_huh DAVE: plans 
      @dave_huh DAVE: what plans
      @rose_idle ROSE: Just some plans.
      @dave_huh DAVE: can i come
      @rose_annoyed ROSE: No!
      @dave_mad DAVE: fuck fine
      @dave_mad DAVE: tomorrow then
      @dave_smug DAVE: maybe ill just dream up my own john tonight and well have an awesome time without you what do you think about that
      @rose_laugh ROSE: ...
      @dave_mad DAVE: fu
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>   
<action class='daveTalk3' sprite='damara' command='talk' name='Talk to Dave.'>
      <args>
      @dave_idle DAVE: hey
      @dave_talk DAVE: who the fuck are you
      @dave_talk DAVE: dont think you belong in here 
      @damara_smile DAMARA: I VERY HAPPY. 
      @damara_smile DAMARA: MEET HUMAN.
      @damara_smile DAMARA: SAY MUCH DELIGHT.
      @dave_talk DAVE: meh you seem harmless enough
      @dave_talk DAVE: what do i even care
      @dave_talk DAVE: go fuck some shit up japanese schoolgirl troll
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>
</classes>
</sburb>