<sburb>
    <classes>
<action class='roseTalk1' sprite='kanaya' command='talk' name='Hablar con Rose.'>
      <args>
      @rose_concern ROSE: &#161;Anda!
      @kanaya2_idle KANAYA: Qu&#233; Ocurre
      @rose_concern ROSE: &#161;Ya no brillas!
      @kanaya2_happy KANAYA: Ah S&#237;
      @kanaya2_smirktalk KANAYA: Estaba Tan Enfrascada En Lo Que Dec&#237;a Mi Antepasada Que Ya Ni Me Acordaba Pero Ahora Ya S&#233; C&#243;mo
      @kanaya2_happy KANAYA: Apagarme
      @rose_talk ROSE: &#191;Has ido a hablar con ella?
      @kanaya2_happy KANAYA: S&#237;
      @rose_happytalk ROSE: &#161;Me alegro! &#191;Qu&#233; tal te ha ido?
      @kanaya2_happy KANAYA: De F&#225;bula
      @kanaya2_happytalk KANAYA: Es Una Persona Encantadora Y Soberbia Como Era De Esperar
      @kanaya2_happytalk KANAYA: Y No Me Sent&#237; Nada Avasallada
      @rose_happytalk ROSE: Le has echado valor; sab&#237;a que no te arrepentir&#237;as.
      @rose_concern ROSE: Y, aparte de c&#243;mo atenuar la piel g&#243;tica, &#191;hablasteis de otra cosa?
      @kanaya2_happy KANAYA: De Muchas M&#225;s
      @kanaya2_happytalk KANAYA: Ante Todo Me Impuls&#243; A Reemprender Mis Responsabilidades
      @rose_idle ROSE: &#191;Ah, s&#237;?
      @kanaya2_happytalk KANAYA: Mi Ancestro Se Opuso Firmemente Al Cometido Con El Que Hab&#237;a Nacido 
      @kanaya2_happytalk KANAYA: A&#250;n Siendo De Distintos Universos La Carga Que Debemos Llevar Sobre Los Hombros Es La Misma
      @kanaya2_happytalk KANAYA: Abandon&#243; Ese Prohibitivo Modo De Vida En Pos Del Libre Albedr&#237;o
      @kanaya2_happytalk KANAYA: Aunque Tambi&#233;n A&#241;adi&#243; Que
      @kanaya2_happytalk KANAYA: No Ten&#237;amos Por Qu&#233; Rechazar Todo Lo Que Nuestra Labor Entra&#241;aba
      @kanaya2_happytalk KANAYA: Comparto Su Opini&#243;n
      @kanaya2_happytalk KANAYA: Mientras Sea Consciente De Mi Libertad
      @kanaya2_happytalk KANAYA: Puedo Aceptar Mi Sino Si Ello Me Motiva A La Superaci&#243;n Personal
      @rose_concern ROSE: &#191;Entonces tienes en mente volver a repoblar la especie troll?
      @rose_concern ROSE: &#191;No dijiste que era una causa perdida?
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: Y Del Orbe No Ha Quedado Nada
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: Ya Me Dijo Ella Que Ser&#237;a Una Ardua Labor
      @kanaya2_smirktalk KANAYA: Pero No Hay Que Perder La Esperanza
      @rose_idle ROSE: En eso lleva raz&#243;n.
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: No S&#233; Ni Por Donde Empezar
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: Pero As&#237; Son Las Aventuras
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: No Se Les Debe Tener Miedo
      @kanaya2_happytalk KANAYA: Lo Que S&#233; Es Que Ganas No Me Faltan
      @rose_happy ROSE: Ya te veo.
      @rose_happytalk ROSE: Te puedo echar una mano cuando lleguemos. Puede que hasta descubramos algo en la otra sesi&#243;n.
      @kanaya2_happy KANAYA: Eso Espero
      @rose_concern ROSE: Oye...
      @rose_sad ROSE: &#191;Te vas a quedar as&#237; para siempre?
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: Ah Descuida Puedo Encenderme Cuando Quiera
      @kanaya_idle KANAYA: Mira
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: No Tiene Mayor Misterio
      @kanaya_happytalk KANAYA: Nuestra Biolog&#237;a No Dejar&#225; De Sorprenderme
      @rose_talk ROSE: Menos mal. Ya me ten&#237;as preocupada.
      @kanaya2_idle KANAYA: Lo Siento
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: S&#233; Que Te Fascinan Las Cosas Que Dan Luz
      @rose_happytalk ROSE: No hay nada como la luz.
      @rose_coytalk ROSE: Y no te lo tomes a mal pero como mi aspecto, ninguno.
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>
<action class='roseTalk2' sprite='dave' command='talk' name='Talk to Rose.'>
      <args>
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: rose quit all the clanking around over here i cant concentrate on my raps
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: what in the sweet religious name of jesus h dick are you doing with all these bottles
      @rose_talk ROSE: Just a little alchemy.
      @dave_huh DAVE: alchemy
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: what kind of shitty thing are you alchemizing with this crap
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: are you alchemizing bottles with other bottles to make like
      @dave_huhtalk:#rose_ebottles DAVE: superbottles
      @rose_annoyedtalk ROSE: No. Believe it or not, I'm actually focused the contents of the bottles.
      @dave_talk DAVE: youre a pretty good hike from the alchemiters
      @rose_talk ROSE: The alchemy I'm practicing is a little more old fashioned.
      @rose_talk ROSE: You know, there was a time on Earth when alchemy didn't refer to a process whereby a large device used game constructs to materialize some idealized version of an object out of thin air.
      @rose_talk ROSE: Alchemists used to experiment with various substances to transmute them into something more valuable.
      @rose_talk ROSE: Its more pedestrian and scientifically credible cousin would be chemistry, which I guess is the technical term for mixing shit together.
      @rose_talk ROSE: Which strictly speaking more accurately describes what I'm doing.
      @dave_talk DAVE: so what your doing science now
      @dave_talk DAVE: who do you think you are your mom
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: wait that sounded like lame burn again
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: every time i talk about your mom it sounds like a burn
      @dave_smug DAVE: who do you think you are my mom
      @dave_huh DAVE: wait scratch that
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: every time we start talking about her as my mom things just start snowballing down our dumb conversational ski slope and suddenly sigmund freud and king oedipus start banging each others hot moms at some kind of depraved sexy momswap party
      @rose_annoyedtalk ROSE: Thanks for the imagery. It was almost as graphic as it made no sense.
      @dave_talk DAVE: so what are you making
      @rose_happy ROSE: Beverages.
      @dave_talk DAVE: beverages what kind of beverages
      @rose_happytalk ROSE: Tasty beverages, I hope.
      @dave_concern DAVE: apple juice???
      @dave_concern DAVE: please let it be aj please let it be aj please let it be aj 
      @rose_talk ROSE: I'll see what I can do.
      @dave_idle DAVE: omg
      @dave_idle:#omg DAVE: omg
      @dave_smug DAVE: fuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuck yes
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>
<action class='roseTalk3' sprite='damara' command='talk' name='Talk to Rose.'>
      <args>
      @rose_talk ROSE: Hello. I don't think we've met.
      @damara_huh DAMARA: 
      @rose_talk ROSE: You seem confused. Are you lost?
      @rose_annoyedtalk ROSE: Maybe you shouldn't be wandering around here.
      @damara_smile DAMARA: PLEASE. APOLOGY.
      @damara_smile DAMARA: NOT WANT. DISTURB YOU.
      @rose_happytalk ROSE: Aw. You seem so sweet.
      @rose_happytalk ROSE: Please, feel free to stay as long as you like.
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>
  	</classes>
</sburb>